{
    "subject": "Ferdinand_II_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Germaine_of_Foix",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand II of Aragon is married to Germaine of Foix.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9843209981918335,
            "question": "Was Ferdinand II of Aragon married to someone named Germaine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9618204832077026,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9617340564727783,
            "question": "What is known about the relationship between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9351524114608765,
            "question": "Is there a historical connection between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115520715713501,
            "question": "Who was Ferdinand II of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9034266471862793,
            "question": "To whom was Germaine of Foix married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8714362978935242,
            "question": "Name a spouse of Ferdinand II of Aragon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8475207090377808,
            "question": "Who was the husband of Germaine of Foix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7962398529052734,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand II of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7512523531913757,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand II of Aragon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand II of Aragon is married to Germaine of Foix.",
            "html": "yago_26316_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Ferdinand II of Aragon's wife?",
            "html": "yago_26316_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the husband of Germaine of Foix?",
            "html": "yago_26316_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a spouse of Ferdinand II of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_26316_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26316_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Ferdinand II of Aragon was indeed married to Germaine of Foix. The documents mention their marriage on multiple occasions and provide details about their relationship, including the birth of a son, John, who died shortly after birth."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Germaine of Foix was the second wife of Ferdinand II of Aragon, thus supporting the statement that Ferdinand II of Aragon is married to Germaine of Foix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}